# DAVID EISENMENGER

**UX DESIGNER** 

### **ABOUT ME**

A user experience designer and researcher with a diverse background in healthcare, social work, and nonprofit management. My focus is to help create seamless user experiences that work well, make people happy, and add value to the product. I have an extensive history focused on wellbeing in the user's experience.

### CONTACT

101 Stevenson Ave Louisville, KY 40206

502.468.4978 david@heronblue.design www.heronblue.design

### **SKILLS**

Research

Interview

Survey

Comparative Analysis

**Usability Testing** 

Design

Persona

Journey Mapping

Wireframing Prototyping

Tools

Sketch

Adobe Creative Suite

InVision

Languages

HTML/CSS JavaScript

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# David Eisenmenger DBA HeronBlue Design

Dec 2017 - Present

Freelance Designer

User experience research and design for clients. Recent projects include user research, interactive design for web and mobile.

# Friendship Health and Rehab

Feb 2016 - April 2019

**Director of Social Services** 

Focus on customer experience and patient wellbeing. Enhanced patient care related to Social Services from the 15th percentile (national) to "deficiency free" status in all 42 areas of Quality of Care as measured by CMS annual survey. (2016-2019)

#### Signature Healthcare, LLC

May 2013 - Feb 2016

Director of Education & Research

Researched, developed, and directed palliative care program piloted at 5 long term care facilities across a regional network. Researched, developed and delivered diversity and inclusion program for use with front line staff in 13 long term care facilities in urban markets.

### Signature Healthcare, LLC

Oct 2009 - May 2013

**Director of Spirituality** 

Led initiatives focused on patient and staff wellbeing. In a high turnover field, average monthly nursing turnover reduced by a 3% in 12 month period. Community Outreach Award for program adding value to the patient, family, community connection. CMS deficiency free annual surveys 2012, 2013.

### **EDUCATION**

User Experience Design Course

May 2018 - April 2019

Springboard

Front End Web Development Track

Sept 2017 - Mar 2018

Code Louisville

M.A. Marriage and Family Therapy

Aug 2005 - May 2007

Louisville Presbyterian Theological Seminary

B.A. Peace and Global Studies

Aug 1999 - May 2001

Earlham College